Guide to the Trustees of Lingnan University Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Photographs, 1898-1973; Series V
  - Individual and Group Portraits
    - Faculty
      - Western faculty: Miscellaneous (R-Z), 1928 (Box 60, Folder 671)
      - Western faculty: Miscellaneous Groups, 1903,1919,1924 (Box 60, Folder 672)
      - Middle School, 1923-1924 (Box 60, Folder 673)
      - Staff Portrait, 1925
      - Miscellaneous committees, councils and groups
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1946 (Box 60, Folder 674)
      - Staff: Medical Related, 1928-1930,n.d. (Box 61, Folder 675)
      - Staff: Sericulture; Launch Workers; Library; Police, 1925-1934 (Box 61, Folder 676)
    - Students
      - Class Groups, 1911-1920 (Box 61, Folder 677)
      - Class Groups, 1921-1924 (Box 61, Folder 678)
      - Class Groups, 1925-1929 (Box 61, Folder 679)
      - Class Groups, 1930-1932 (Box 61, Folder 680)
      - Class Groups, 1933-1935 (Box 61, Folder 681)
      - Class Groups, 1936-1937 (Box 61, Folder 682)
      - Alumni, 1911-1936 (Box 62, Folder 683)
      - Athletics, 1905,1920-1928 (Box 62, Folder 684)
      - Athletics, 1929-1956 (Box 62, Folder 685)
      - Athletics, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 686)
      - Boys Day Committee, 1903-1930 (Box 62, Folder 687)
      - Boy Scouts
      - Clubs: Chemistry, 1927-1938 (Box 62, Folder 688)
      - Clubs: Co-Eds
      - Clubs: Educational
      - Clubs: Political Science
      - Exchange Programs, 1934-1938 (Box 62, Folder 689)
      - Former Students, 1909-1927 (Box 62, Folder 690)
      - Medical Related, 1911 (Box 62, Folder 691)
      - Middle School, 1931-1934
      - Military Organizations, 1917-1940 (Box 62, Folder 692)
      - Music Related Organizations: Band, Choir, 1920-1938 (Box 62, Folder 693)
      - Student Christian Association and School, 1917-1927 (Box 63, Folder 694)
      - Student Union, 1924-1934 (Box 63, Folder 695)
      - Women at Canton Christian College (See also: OVERSIZE), 1903-1938 (Box 63, Folder 696-697)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977,n.d. (Box 63, Folder 698)
      - Students at Graduation Trustees and Directors (Box OV1)
    - Trustees and Directors
      - Frank, Henry S., n.d. (Box 63, Folder 699)
      - Graybill, Henry B. and Family, 1916-1920 (Box 63, Folder 700)
      - Gressitt, J. Linsley, 1940
      - Groff Family, 1916-1933 (Box 63, Folder 701)
      - Henry, James and Family, 1928-1931 (Box 63, Folder 702)
      - Hoffmann, William E., 1925 (Box 63, Folder 703)
      - Knipp, Arthur R., n.d. (Box 63, Folder 704)
      - Laird, Clinton N., 1905-1930 (Box 63, Folder 705)
      - Pride, Richard E., n.d. (Box 63, Folder 706)
      - Wannamaker, Olin D.
      - Miscellaneous, 1922-1966 (Box 63, Folder 707)
    - Benefactors and Donors
      - Various, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 708)
    - Visitors
      - from Hainan, 1934 (Box 64, Folder 709)
      - Governor of Hong Kong, 1957
      - Paul Lau, 1957
      - Yorke Allen, 1978
      - Miscellaneous (including President Sun Yat-sen), 1921-1938 (Box 64, Folder 710)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Children, Refugees, Village Work Group, 1913-1939 (Box 64, Folder 711)
      - Lingnan Hospital; Village Hospital, 1931-1938 (Box 64, Folder 712)
      - Teachers' Summer Institute; General Studies Association; Agricultural Leaders; Christian Association Activities, 1929-1937 (Box 64, Folder 713)
      - Miscellaneous Groups, 1900-1934 (Box 64, Folder 714)
      - Miscellaneous Groups: Unidentified, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 715)
      - Miscellaneous Individuals, 1909-1931 (Box 64, Folder 716)
      - Miscellaneous Individuals: Unidentified (Box 64, Folder 717)
- Addendum, Series VI
  - Canton Medical Missions Society, Canton Hospital, & the Medical School
    - Canton Medical Missionary Society, 1897-1950 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - The Medical School in Canton (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - University Medical School President's report 1910-1911 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Canton Hospital
      - Treatment Records (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Relationship with CMMS & LU (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Financial statements and fees (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Fundraising and development materials (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Other (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Canton Christian College
    - The Graduates of the CCC Middle School, 1901-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - CCC relationship with Ling Naam Council, 1912 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Woman Student Friendship Association (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Catalogue (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with CCC trustees, 1885, 1913-1916 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Freshman Annual, 1919 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - CCC Student Publications, 1923 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Canton College News (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Fundraising and Development Materials (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Report of the President, 1901-1902, 1902-1903, 1919-1924 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Canton Christian College: Its Growth and Outlook, progress report, 1912-1919 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Lingnan University
    - University Staff (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Catalogue, 1934-1935, 1937-1938 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Curriculum Materials (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Directory of Students, 1935 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Lingnan University & the refugee community, 1938-1941 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - William Henry Grant (Father of Lingnan) (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Commencement bulletins, 1931, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Funeral Service of President Chung, 1941 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - English Language Student Publications, 1935 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Christian Activity at Lingnan University (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Pacific Area Exchange Students Lingnan newsletters vo 2, no 1, 2, & 5 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - CCC/LU and the Silk Industry (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Women's Leadership (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees
      - List of trustees, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Reports to the Trustees, 1923, 1927, 1938-1940 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Publications
        - Short Promotional Materials (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Lingnan Newsletter (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Lingnan University: a romantic achievement of Chinese and American Cooperation (illustrated historical sketch), 1941 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - The Spirit and Purpose of Lingnan, 1928 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Items about Canton Christian College/Lingnan University (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - The China Colleges, 1935 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Photographs (Box 68, Folder 7)